<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Chandler Justice</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Chandler Justice</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 20:01:22 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on Digital Minimalism</title>
      <link>/posts/digitalminimalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 20:01:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/digitalminimalism/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I read the fantastic self help/philosophy book Digital Minimalism By Cal Newport. This book takes the ideas and lifestyle choices minimalism dictates and applies them to our modern digital age; wherein we are constantly bombarded with information. I wanted to share some thoughts I have had since reading this book and explain some philosophies behind my relationship with technology.
Introduction By and large, when someone gets on their phone or computer recreationally they do not get on with an idea in mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Created Instant Rice, An Automatic Theming Tool</title>
      <link>/posts/instantrice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 18:02:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/instantrice/</guid>
      <description>The amount of customization available on a Linux desktop absolutely scratches my OCD. I sometimes find myself spending hours tweaking every aspect of the system I can. Every program that dropped a file in my .config folder was a new present, where I could dive in and change every last variable of a configuration value. Beyond scratching an itch, tweaking a program&amp;rsquo;s config file is a great way to learn how that program works and how to use that program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;23: Semester Retrospective</title>
      <link>/posts/fall23review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 10:31:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/fall23review/</guid>
      <description>This semester was a lot of fun for me. I am going to go through some of the highlights and lowlights of this last semester in anticipation of the upcoming semester. I also completed all the requirements for my Bachelors in Computer Science, so from here on out all my coursework will be towards completing my second degree in Computational Math.
CS5030: High Performance Computing Taught by Dr. Steve Patruzza This class was a blast and goes head first into high performance computing and the best practices when utilizing a computing cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the website</title>
      <link>/posts/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 18:02:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hello/</guid>
      <description>This is my new personal website where I hope to babble and provide mildly insightful blog posts and other materials.
To build this site I used Hugo. The theme is a modified variant of hugo-xmin.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
