<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Chandler Justice</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Chandler Justice</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 18:02:40 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How I Created Instant Rice, An Automatic Theming Tool</title>
      <link>/posts/instantrice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 18:02:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/instantrice/</guid>
      <description>The amount of customization available on a Linux desktop absolutely scratches my OCD. I sometimes find myself spending hours tweaking every aspect of the system I can. Every program that dropped a file in my .config folder was a new present, where I could dive in and change every last variable of a configuration value. Beyond scratching an itch, tweaking a program&amp;rsquo;s config file is a great way to learn how that program works and how to use that program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;23: Semester Retrospective</title>
      <link>/posts/fall23review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 10:31:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/fall23review/</guid>
      <description>This semester was a lot of fun for me. I am going to go through some of the highlights and lowlights of this last semester in anticipation of the upcoming semester. I also completed all the requirements for my Bachelors in Computer Science, so from here on out all my coursework will be towards completing my second degree in Computational Math.
CS5030: High Performance Computing Taught by Dr. Steve Patruzza This class was a blast and goes head first into high performance computing and the best practices when utilizing a computing cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the website</title>
      <link>/posts/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 18:02:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hello/</guid>
      <description>This is my new personal website where I hope to babble and provide mildly insightful blog posts and other materials.
To build this site I used Hugo. The theme is a modified variant of hugo-xmin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Chandler Justice</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I have a strong passion for all things computer science and mathematics. I am fascinated by the problems that can be solved by the tools these disciplines provide.
Topics I am particularly fond of include: Operating Systems (Specifically UNIX) Back End development I love languages like C, C++, Rust, etc Graph Theory Computational Mathematics Hacking devices back into relevance using aftermarket software. Education BS: Computer Science | Utah State | Fall 2019 - Fall 2023</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading List</title>
      <link>/reading-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reading-list/</guid>
      <description>This will serve as a rolling archive of the books I have read, when I read them, and any reflections I had while reading.
The Naked Sun - Isaac Asimov (1957)
ISBN 0-553-29339-7 Read Summer 2023 I read this book a while ago so my thoughts on it are kind of rusty. I found this book to be really eye opening especially with the context of the pandemic. A persistent theme of the book is more and more of people&amp;rsquo;s daily lives being facilitated by robots, resulting in a society which practices extremely germaphobic behaviors including only communicating via video conferencing; a striking parallel to society during the 2020 pandemic, except replace a 1950s interpretation of Zoom with&amp;hellip; Zoom.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
